

Ralph Rallion
Dela Cruz Laynes

Web Application Developer

- ralphlaynes@gmail.com
- 09184759946
- 28 Bonifacio Street Brgy. Del Carmen Pagbilao, Quezon
- rallion90.github.io/myPortfolio/port folio.html

SKILLS

- Web Technologies PHP, Laravel, Codeigniter, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Materialize, JQuery.
- Task Tool Asana, Clickup.
- Knowledge in Linux OS and Windows OS.
- Software and Hardware Troubleshooting.
- Advance Understanding in Microsoft Office

EDUCATION

Manuel S. Enverga University Foundation / Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Enverga Blvd. Ibabang Dupay, Lucena City, Philippines 2015 - 2020

Casa Del Nino Jesus De Pagbilao / Highschool

CM Recto Street, Brgy. 1 Castillo (POB.), 4302 Pagbilao, Quezon 2011 - 2015

Summary

Web Developer with a passion for web application development especially backend with over 1-year development experience. Proficient in Developing Backend System for the Client needs. I already finished 4 projects including my capstone/thesis using Core PHP, Codeigniter and Laravel. I can also make Development Plan and Process that suits for the Client's need.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer – Intern (600 hrs.)

Magellan Solutions / February 2020 to April 2020 – Mandaluyong

- Creating Website Functionality using Laravel Framework and Javascript.
- Help employee inside the department with computer related problem.
- Database Management.
- Collaborate with other developers inside the company.
- Answering Inbound Call from the clients.
- Developed Plan that can be useful for the Agents to Manage the Room Reservation inside the company.

Web Developer Assistant – Intern (240 hrs.)

RGRR Web Maker / June 2017 to August 2017 – Lucena, City

- Building functional website.
- Creating website functionality using CorePHP and Javascript.
- Website Optimization.
- Building Landing page using WordPress.
- Microsoft Office Works.
- Data Entry.

References

SC Camille Gollena Perez

Control Staff – Waltermart 09070154074

Cleobert Dela Cruz

Web Developer - Magellan 09463955341

Mayeth Pionilla

Master Teacher I – Pagbilao Elementary School 09186901332